<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teddy&#39;s online desktop</title>
    <link>https://www.codelooper.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Teddy&#39;s online desktop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.codelooper.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Global size of agriculture insurance market in 2020 and beyond</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/global-size-of-agriculture-insurance-market-in-2020-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/global-size-of-agriculture-insurance-market-in-2020-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>People often ask me how large is the world wide agriculture insurance market. U.S., Canada, China, and India have large government subsidized programs and provide reports on premiums. However, the reports do not contain privately sold products and premiums. These are mostly hail and top-up programs that complement the government subsidized crop and livestock insurance programs.
Roman Shynkarenko provided the post below on Linkedin for the agriculture insurance market in 2020 according to Allianz (32bn world wide in 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat XL pricing using rate on line (ROL) curves</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/cat-xl-pricing-using-rate-on-line-curves/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/cat-xl-pricing-using-rate-on-line-curves/</guid>
      <description>When I was working with stop loss reinsurance contracts the usual way to perform the pricing exercise would be to gather all the loss data, fit a loss distribution to that data, make adjustments based on seasonal outlook or other variables, and apply the limits and retentions asked by the clients/brokers.
Although this is standard practice and almost second nature, another way to look at the pricing problem is from the point of view that you, as an underwriter, do not have all the information and perhaps should take into consideration market pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarto</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-15-quarto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-15-quarto/</guid>
      <description>Checking out Quarto today. It looks like a more comprehensive tool than R Markdown though it does a lot of similar things like being able to write text and include code cells (like Jupyter), but then also able to render the output into many formats (pdf, html, word, etc) using Pandoc. I guess that makes sense since it’s published by the same folks behind R Markdown and R Studio:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R blogdown and GitHub</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken all day to get blogdown to sync with GitHub. I already had a repo set up at https://tedtwong.github.io/ and I had set up a blogdown folder in R Studio, let’s call it: R/blogdown.
I wasn’t too familiar with how to set up git to sync the R/blogdown/public folder with https://tedtwong.github.io/ repo so that I can version control blogdown files and host the files on GitHub at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2020-12-01-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Sample</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2017-03-05-math-sample/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2017-03-05-math-sample/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;KaTeX can be used to generate complex math formulas server-side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
\phi = \frac{(1+\sqrt{5})}{2} = 1.6180339887\cdots
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
e^{i\pi} = -1
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional details can be found on
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Khan/KaTeX&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; or on the
&lt;a href=&#34;http://tiddlywiki.com/plugins/tiddlywiki/katex/&#34;&gt;Wiki&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/page/about/</guid>
      <description>A work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
