<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Teddy&#39;s online desktop</title>
    <link>https://www.codelooper.com/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Teddy&#39;s online desktop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.codelooper.com/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Analytics Certificate</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/google-data-analytics-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/google-data-analytics-certificate/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finally completed the Coursera Google Data Analytics Certificate.
I think the course is great for beginners in data analytics. For me it was a great refresher on SQL and R but the other sections were not all that useful. The course did motivate me to delve a bit more into R and this blog site is probably a little bit in response to that.
I think the course could use a bit more on statistical thinking and diving a bit deeper into probability since data analysts could really use that in their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Shiny R within blogdown</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/running-shiny-within-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/running-shiny-within-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>I just learned that I could embed the R Shiny app into blogdown from this post. So here’s an attempt at that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarto</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-15-quarto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-15-quarto/</guid>
      <description>Checking out Quarto today. It looks like a more comprehensive tool than R Markdown though it does a lot of similar things like being able to write text and include code cells (like Jupyter), but then also able to render the output into many formats (pdf, html, word, etc) using Pandoc. I guess that makes sense since it’s published by the same folks behind R Markdown and R Studio:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R blogdown and GitHub</title>
      <link>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.codelooper.com/post/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/2022-07-14-blogdown-github/</guid>
      <description>It’s taken all day to get blogdown to sync with GitHub. I already had a repo set up at https://tedtwong.github.io/ and I had set up a blogdown folder in R Studio, let’s call it: R/blogdown.
I wasn’t too familiar with how to set up git to sync the R/blogdown/public folder with https://tedtwong.github.io/ repo so that I can version control blogdown files and host the files on GitHub at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
